Contact

berannvic@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/victory-hayden-200b46a6 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel

Victory Hayden

Registered Nurse at Red River ER

Durant, Oklahoma

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the medical practice industry. Skilled in Nursing, Event Planning, Microsoft Excel, Customer Service, and Management. Strong healthcare services professional with a Applied Science focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Murray State College.

Experience

Red River ER
Registered Nurse
April 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)
2022 N. Hwy. 75 Sherman, TX 75090

Alliance Health of Durant RN August 2014 - Present (6 years) Emergency Room

Total Medical Personnel Staffing Registered Nurse August 2012 - February 2016 (3 years 7 months) Ada, Oklahoma

Education

Murray State College

Applied Science, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2013 - 2014)

Kiamichi Technology Center-Durant LPN/LVN, Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse Training · (2010 - 2011)

Grayson College

General Studies, General Studies · (2005 - 2008)